Las Encinas is reopening
and aims to get back to normal,
according to an official statement
by the school.
I can't believe this happened.
Two weeks later, there is still
little information about the shooting.
Fortunately, there were no injuries.
We'll update you as the story develops.
My sister went to that school too.
Now she's living her best life.
- And look at me.
- It will pass.
- The hard times won't last forever.
- When will the pain go away, Mateo?
I'm thinking about going back on my meds.
I still have some left.
You don't need pills.
Let alone to self-medicate.
When will I stop having nightmares,
fucking anxiety,
a black cloud hanging over my head?
You need to live through it now.
Don't run away. Sit with it.
You'll be moving on before you know it.
I'm telling you,
Las Encinas is a safe place.
How can you be so sure?
I don't know
why we're still discussing this.
Our children's lives are in danger.
- María, please.
- No.
Dídac needs to be expelled.
- Mom!
- Not now, Nico. Please.
Having a member
of a crime family here is-
What do you mean?
- It was all over the news.
- It's not true.
- Dídac's parents are business owners.
- He's just a kid.
Look, whatever your name is…
- I'm Luis, the head of studies.
- Whatever.
They targeted Las Encinas
because they know Dídac goes here.
So either he leaves,
or we'll find another school for our kids.
- Simple as that.
- We have no choice.
- No, María.
- What else can we do?
Take some time to think this over.
We'll have a vote in two days.
And if you want someone
to vote on your behalf…
These two, for example.
That's fine.
Okay, but in the meantime,
keep him away from the other students.
Thank you, everyone.
We'll resume this discussion
once you've reached a decision.
- This has gotten out of hand.
- Dídac.
This is unbelievable.
Why can't you stay out of my life?
- You need to stop!
- Hey, relax. Cool it.
I'll get expelled,
and Dad will make me come home to Jávea.
What the hell are you guys involved in?
You're not going anywhere.
You didn't answer my question.
If you don't want to get mixed up in this,
that's fine by me.
But then don't ask me for details.
- I made real friends here.
- You won't have to leave.
Trust me.
This can't be happening.
It's completely unfair.
I mean, we are talking about
people with guns.
Everyone, back to your seats, please.
Nico, could I borrow
those pictures of you and Dídac?
I'll give them back.
I just want to do what I can to help him.
Thanks.
Nico.
I think it's awesome
that you're standing up for Dídac.
He's my best friend.
It's nice to be around people
who would do anything for their friends.
CHECK OUT THE SLUTTY NEW GIRL…
Why'd all our phones blow up
at the same time?
It has an explicit content warning.
It's probably a throwaway account.
I bet it's revenge porn.
Don't watch it.
It's a violation of her privacy.
Well, I'm gonna check it out.
Come on, Sara. Don't.
Are you recording?
You're into that, huh?
Okay. That's enough.
It took you a minute to stop me.
Looks like you wanted to watch too.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Hey, that video thing was messed up.
I can't imagine how you're feeling.
Oh, I'm not pressed.
I won't lose any sleep over it.
If that happened to me, I'd be devastated.
Someone stole my phone the other day.
I knew this could happen, and it did.
It is what it is. I'm over it.
- I'm Chloe, by the way.
- Sonia.
Nice to meet you.
Thanks for caring.
We can't enjoy the pool in this weather.
Don't worry. We'll be fine in here.
At least the company's good.
Any excuse to see you. Cheers.
Now, these are what I call ice cubes.
Not what you get abroad.
Spanish ice cubes are amazing.
Come on. Don't be naughty.
When I'm good, I'm very good.
But when I'm naughty, I'm even better.
Cheers.
Hi, Mom.
Hi!
Honey, you remember José Luis, right?
He looks familiar.
She was just a kid then.
Wow. You're all grown up now.
Well, yeah.
I filled out nicely, huh?
Why don't you head out?
I have to talk to José Luis.
Sure.
Good to see you, José Luis.
Same here.
Eyes on me.
Is my daughter gone?
What?
Carmen, please!
I get all clumsy
when I'm around jerks like you.
- I didn't say anything.
- I know what you were thinking.
You're unbelievable.
Come here, silly.
You wouldn't happen to have a spare suit
from one of your other lovers, would you?
Careful, or you might end up eating
this pleated skirt.
Then I guess I'll have to take a taxi home
looking like this.
See you tomorrow?
Come on, silly.
Let's meet tomorrow
and discuss what brought you to Madrid.
- I know it's not me.
- Clever boy.
Bye.
Welcome home.
- Need help?
- No, I'm good.
Okay.
- Should I leave your stuff here?
- Sure.
- You hungry?
- Yeah. Let's order out.
I'm starving.
I could really go for some pizza.
- Sounds good.
- Awesome.
Surprise!
Thanks, everyone.
The police say
there's evidence against Patrick
and that the burned car was his,
but I know he didn't do it.
Right, but he did disappear
with his family right after.
I'm just saying, it's suspicious.
I don't care. There's no way he did it.
He would never do that to you.
Iván, I…
I'm sorry.
I'm truly so sorry.
I mean it.
I'm sorry you had to go through so much
in such a short time.
I'll be right back.
I'll go check on her.
What was that?
What the hell was that?
Were you gonna confess?
Well, this is great.
Just fucking great.
I can't do this.
Oh, you can't?
Poor you.
You think you're the only one suffering?
You wanna go to the police? Let's go.
But I'll confess.
- What?
- Yeah. I'll say I did it.
Wait, why?
So we can put an end to this.
I just won't let you ruin your life.
I fucking refuse.
I swear I'll go to jail instead.
I'll kill myself if I have to.
Listen to me.
If we stick together, nobody has to pay.
The worst is over. I promise.
Trust me.
Okay?
SCHOOL OF SOCIAL WORK
For tomorrow, make sure
you've read up on the Frankfurt School.
Thank you.
Omar. The department was just contacted
about a paid internship.
Las Encinas is looking for someone
to manage their new student support app.
You studied there, right?
No, I didn't.
Really? I thought I'd read it in-
No. Sorry.
I guess I was mistaken.
Anyway, call this number
if you're interested.
Thanks, but I'm not.
HEAD OF STUDIES
Why did you want these?
Nico's grown into a remarkable young man,
thanks to the role models he has at home.
But at this stage in his life,
he needs peers.
Friends who treat him as an equal.
And I think that's what Dídac is for Nico.
Look…
it'd be unfair for a student
to pay for his family's reputation.
And for another to lose a friend
due to his parents' stubbornness.
END SPECULATION
People without homes!
Homes without people!
RIOT IN A SQUAT
Squatters claim the building,
located in an area known as Madrid Río,
is now a community center.
In fact, those in…
María?
What?
- Did you see that?
- What?
…about the meaning of the name,
they claim the center has made…
Let me go!
…of support for the neighborhood.
RIOT IN A SQUAT
Thanks so much.
Eric.
- Hi, Aunt María.
- Hi.
Are you all right?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah?
And your parents?
They don't know I'm here.
What do you mean?
I'll call them.
No, I don't want them to find out.
They're not a part of my life anymore.
Where are you living?
Wherever I can crash.
How's cousin Nico?
He's doing well.
He's… very happy.
I'm so proud of him.
Let's go home.
Seriously?
- Can't you remember?
- Sent.
Thanks.
You okay, Sara?
Yeah. I just overreact sometimes.
Don't worry, babe,
We're all kind of extra here.
- Pizza and playlists, anyone?
- Please.
Is that the pizza already?
Hello.
Hi.
Nico texted me.
I wanted to come give Iván a hug.
- Hey, Dídac.
- How are you doing?
- Hanging in there.
- It's great to see you.
Come on in. Everyone's here.
- Cool.
- See you in there.
What?
It's his last night here.
Are you really going to keep avoiding him?
Iván, stay out of this.
Wait, Isa.
Look… I know what it's like
to come to terms with losing someone.
All the things
you'll never get to do together.
It's incredibly painful. You have no idea.
And you?
How are you?
Do you need some space?
- I'm glad you all came, but-
- I'll kick them out in three minutes.
Hello.
Eric!
Nico!
What's up? You staying for dinner?
He's moving in with us.
- Really?
For how long?
We'll see. Just temporarily.
Please? We'll talk it over later.
It takes some serious guts
to go up against cops in full riot gear.
Weren't you scared?
We have to stand up to injustice, man.
If we don't fight, the bad guys win.
Yeah, true.
So you hung in there until the very end?
I was the one running the show there.
How could I bail on them?
I would've freaked out.
"If we don't fight, the bad guys win."
Good guys and bad guys.
He's violent and immature.
Why'd you bring him here?
What else could I do?
He had nowhere else to go.
Well, maybe there's a reason
your brother kicked him out.
Eric's a good kid.
Maybe being with Nico and us, in a home
where he feels cared for and loved,
will help him find his focus.
- Or make Nico lose his.
- That won't happen.
Nico has common sense
and knows what he wants in life.
It's just a few weeks.
We can see how it goes,
and then we'll decide.
Mom. Eric and I are going out.
Okay, honey.
It's Dídac's last night,
so we're all going to Isadora's place.
- Don't stay out too late.
- Okay.
Just let me get changed.
María,
I know Eric's family, but you should
be kinder to your son's best friend.
Unlike Eric, Dídac is a good influence.
Hello, my love.
I've written a thousand letters
on my phone,
and I've thought up a thousand speeches
to convince you to take me back.
But in the end, this is me saying goodbye.
I refuse to lose you forever.
Even if it's for the best.
Let me live with the hope
that we'll meet again.
I'm not asking for something we never had.
I'm not asking for something new.
I just want to go back
to what we once had.
Something that was real.
But for that to happen…
I have to disappear.
That's what everyone says.
So, until we see each other again…
I love you.
I love you so much, Iván.
I always have, and I always will.
Hello?
- Yeah?
- Hi. Did you order pizza?
Yeah, but… I can't get up. I need help.
Could you use the door code and come in?
It's one-nine-nine-seven.
Oh my God. Are you okay?
Should I just… take you?
I mean… take you inside.
- Inside the house.
- Okay.
Come on, then.
Let's go. One, two…
- Thanks. Oh, God.
- There. You good?
Damn. This place is huge.
You live here by yourself?
Yeah.
Sorry. It's none of my business.
No worries.
Tell me where to leave the pizzas,
and I'll get going.
Right there is fine.
Hey… have you had dinner?
Do you wanna stay?
I ordered way too much pizza.
- Shit. Did I come on too strong?
- No.
Sure. I'm down.
I mean, I could skip a few orders.
Cool.
Where's the kitchen?
I'll grab some beers. If you have any.
I do. It's down there.
- Great.
- Right at the end.
Where are you going?
Let me see that.
It's nothing.
If only you weren't so stubborn…
I'm going to Isadora's.
Why? We already saw Iván.
To hang out with my friends.
See how stubborn you are?
Come on.
It takes us forever to pick a movie.
- Hi.
- Hey, babe.
Everybody, this is Chloe.
I wanted her to meet you all.
How's it going?
The police are the arm of a fascist state
that capitalizes on people's lives.
Jesus…
You okay?
Yeah, but I'm heading downstairs.
Twerking is my thing,
not talking politics.
Coming?
No? It's all good. You do you.
Glad she wanted to hang with us.
Yeah.
I'm gonna run.
I have some stuff to do. Tonight was fun.
- I'm gonna get a drink.
- They have table service, man.
COME TO MY SUITE.
Nature calls.
I'm gonna bounce too.
I've got to…
Yeah, I'm out.
- Looks like everyone ditched us.
- I know, right?
I never got a chance to thank you.
For what? Not flipping out
when you used me to get with Ari?
Wow.
Sorry. That sounded
less passive-aggressive in my head.
It was just a friendly jab.
You're talking about
the day I stopped you at the clinic.
I did it to remind you that the Nico
I met was happy with who he was.
Just the way he was.
What?
There must be a reason you came over here.
I've been thinking about the video thing.
It sucks.
Yeah, I'm not happy about it.
The video was supposed to be private.
But I'm not ashamed. It was just sex.
- Have you seen it?
- What?
The video.
No. I haven't.
Do you want to?
- What?
- I mean, everyone else has.
That way, it won't be such a big deal.
And I'll tell you what.
It's no wonder it got leaked.
It's fucking hot.
- It's your video.
- Yeah, but I want to show you.
Wanna see it or not?
Come on. Let's go somewhere more private.
What? Like it?
- How can you be so open about it?
- You're pretty open about watching it.
Come on. Tell the truth.
It turned you on, right?
This is who I am.
Take it…
or leave it.
Fuck me.
- Hold up.
- What?
I'd like to get to know you
over some drinks first.
Do you want to get to know me
or tell me all about you?
So you can impress me
and make me fall hard for you?
Feeling admired turns you on.
Turning people on turns me on.
Why do I want to inherit millions
when all that money
can't bring back what I've lost?
Yeah, but… you have a house.
And the money can help you pay
for professional help
to get over your loss.
Or guarantee you a stable future.
You know what, Iván?
I don't have a future
or money to secure it.
I just have to survive, day by day.
I don't know.
Maybe money doesn't buy happiness,
but it comes pretty close.
Shit, I'm sorry. I meant to cheer you up,
not be a downer.
- Don't worry.
- Want me to go?
No. Stay.
I hardly know you,
but I like being with you.
Same.
Shut up!
Let me go.
You and I are gonna talk.
Now, keep it down.
Easy.
I mean, yeah.
Life keeps giving us signs
that we're not meant to be together.
Maybe those signs
are telling us we can overcome
any obstacle that stands in our way.
Because here we are again. Together.
And you're right.
Things shouldn't be this difficult
or whatever.
I know.
Okay, then.
Goodbye, Isadora.
No, wait. Don't leave.
I can't let you go like that.
Wait. Now you need to turn right.
A little further ahead.
A little more.
Here.
I'm gonna hit the dance floor.
- Did I do something wrong?
- No, it's just…
I can't do this. I'm sorry.
No. Let's stop.
What's wrong?
I can't do this.
I don't know why, but I can't.
You're just not ready yet. It's okay.
But I want this.
I really do. And I want it to be with you.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have kissed you.
It's okay. Don't worry.
There's nothing to be sorry about.
I wanted it too.
Can I have a second?
It's been a while
since I clicked with someone like this.
So I'd like it if we could be friends.
Just friends, okay? I promise.
Cool. Fine by me.
Great.
Cool. Friends, then.
And as your new friend,
I'd like to do something meaningful
with my money…
and help you secure the future
you thought you'd never have.
Hey.
Wanna grab a drink sometime? Just to talk.
I won't hijack the conversation next time.
We could get to know each other.
We'll see, okay?
What's your IG? Or your…?
You should be careful with those videos.
We all know what could happen.
And you should mind your own business.
We barely just met,
and you're being kinda clingy.
I leaked that video myself.
- M'kay?
- What?
Okay, Mom.
Don't you always tell me
to find a rich boyfriend?
I can get a few of those in Las Encinas.
You think it's okay
to expose yourself like that?
I got the attention of the whole school.
Three out of four students want me.
If I ever taught you anything,
it's to respect yourself.
And that we have a lot to offer.
More than just that.
Really? Like what?
What else do we have, Mom?
We're nothing but bodies.
That's what they want from us,
and we take advantage of that.
Besides, I learned from the best.
Pamela, Paris, Kim.
And you, Mom.
I learned all this from you.
Whatever you say
or do to try to convince me,
I can't issue you
the pension from Cruz after his death.
Do you think I was born yesterday?
Of course you can.
You were his lawyer.
It's impossible. Period.
Impossible.
The idiots' adjective.
Look, Carmen. I can't and I won't.
I guess this means
you won't want to see me again.
The contract I signed
with your father and Cruz
said that I'd get my pension
as long as I stayed away from my son.
That's what it said, right?
That's correct.
Okay. So no pension, no deal.
Nothing can stop me from approaching him.
Joel.
This came for you.
Jeez.
YOUR FUTURE
YOUR FRIEND, IVÁN
What is it?
- Can you explain it to me?
- What is there to explain?
Dalmar, can you give us a minute?
- Talk in your room.
- Please.
I'm out. I'm not letting
your drama ruin my morning.
So?
Look, I don't remember when I applied,
but I did, and that's it.
You didn't mention it.
Do I need your permission to aspire
to be more than a delivery boy?
How can you afford it?
I got a scholarship.
What scholarship?
You applied for one and didn't tell me?
I wasn't sure I'd get it.
So pick a different school.
- What? Why?
- There are tons of good schools.
- Forget about Las Encinas.
- What's the problem, Omar?
Why would I turn down a spot
at the top school?
Shit.
So, you studied there.
You always told me
you went to public school.
Was that all a lie?
Look. I didn't tell you I applied,
and you didn't tell me you went there.
We're even.
I never talk about that place
because it messed me up.
Me and people I loved very much.
Joel, please don't go there.
I don't know what happened to you
or those people you loved.
But not everyone who attends Las Encinas
has a rough time.
That school churns out
successful graduates.
It's not right
that you're trying to hold me back.
What if they fuck you up too?
What if they don't?
What if, for the first time ever,
I can have a dream?
That place changes people.
Omar…
I… know exactly who I am.
Okay?
I won't let anyone change me.
Look. I'll go, get my degree,
and make the most of it.
If you love me,
then trust me and have my back.
Welcome.
Thanks.
Want a tour?
That'd be great.
When will I stop having nightmares,
fucking anxiety,
a black cloud hanging over my head?
You need to live through it now.
Don't run away. Sit with it.
What if I try exposure therapy?
Going back there and facing it?
It'd do more harm than good.
You need to protect yourself for now.
Stay away from all that.
Good morning.
Are you Luis, the head of studies?
Yes, that's me.
I'm from the School of Social Work.
I'm here about the internship
to run the school's app.
Okay. Your name is?
I'm Omar.
All right. Take a seat.
Okay, how are you going to vote?
Your votes and any proxies.
To… let Dídac stay.
Roberta?
Same thing. Let him stay.
I hope this is for the best.
María, as head of studies,
I'll be on top of every student.
NIGHTCLUBS
I'll ensure their safety and well-being.
RAMOS VICO FAMILY
You can take my word for it.
TRIPS TO MADRID
Subtitle translation by: Toni Navarro,
Meredith Cannella